We're going to take some fresh garlic; we need about 6-7 cloves of garlic.
I love garlic and everything, heck I'll put garlic in my cereal if I could.
When we come back, we're going to take some garlic and chop it up.
So we have our fresh garlic if you just give it a good break you can see all the cloves come out we need about 6 7 cloves.
We're going to take our clove of garlic just give it a good punch with our knife and you see it comes right out of the shell like so and what you might want to do is just cut off this tip.
So that's a hard tip from the stem and that's your garlic getting ready for chopping, get another punch and you see it comes right out of the shell.
What you're going to do then now is just slice your garlic one way, very thin slices.
Don't cut yourself, turn it the other way just like we did with our onion and just cut your garlic.
Don't worry again if it isn't a desired consistency of size because we'll start to do is using our chopping method is work the back of the blade and chop this up real fine.
So this is what 6 cloves or 7 cloves of garlic looks like finely minced.
See how nice and tiny and beautiful?
We're just going to add this right to our bowl so don't be afraid just come right here, look at that.
What we're going to do then is start mixing it all together.